searchregistry.org 2014-06-26

# Privacypolicy

**By registering and using this site, you explicitly accept, without limitation or qualification, the collection, use, and transfer of personal information provided by you in the manner described in this statement. Please read the following statement to ensure that you agree with the way we collect and process personal information. If you do not agree, your only recourse is not to use this site or its services.**

This policy applies to this website and regulates the processing of information relating to you and grants both us and you various rights with respect to your personal data. It describes what type of information we collect; how we use that information and to whom we can provide that information. It also informs you of how to notify us to stop using your information. Our company is located in the United States. You may be located in a country that has laws which are more restrictive about the collection and use of your personal information. However, by using our site, you agree to waive the more restrictive laws and agree to be governed by the laws of the United States.

This Site may also posts links to other web sites over which we have no control. As such, we are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other web sites when you choose to link from this site. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those other web sites so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information. We also do not control the data use practices of those persons or entities who may access your information on this site for the purposes of providing the service or product you have requested or third party Ad Networks and other third parties with whom we work to serve you personalized ads on our site. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and opt-out choices of those third parties so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information

**Information We Collect and Retain**

We collect your personal information and demographic information you choose to provide us. We also collect information about how you use our site and the areas of our site that you visit. We do not sell your personal information. We only use the information that you provide to us, and you consent to the use of that information by providing it to us.

**How Your Information is Used**

Information you provide us upon registration for services and products listed on our site, post in public areas of the site, or placed in a searchable database will be accessed, used, and stored by others around the world. We use commercially reasonable practices to provide a safe, secure environment by limiting access to our database to authorized persons with whom we are in a contractual relationship, but cannot guarantee that unauthorized parties will not gain access. We also cannot control how authorized persons store or transfer information downloaded from the database, so you should ensure that you do not post sensitive information to our site. We use the information we collect about you to deliver the products and services we offer, and to operate and improve our site. Our services may include the display of personalized content and advertising. We may use your information to contact you about site updates, conduct surveys, or informational and service-related communications, including important security updates.

**Disclosure of Information to Others**

We share your information with third parties who deliver the products and services you have requested. These third parties may not use your information for any purpose other than assisting us in providing those products and services. We may also use your information to contact you about other products or services available from third parties. We may also share your information with third parties who may contact you about their products or services. We also share information where legally required. Information collected on our Sites is stored in whole or in part in the United States, and therefore subject to U.S. law. Finally, we may disclose and transfer information if our business is sold or acquired.

**Your Choices About Your Information**

You may delete the personal information you submit to us at any time by notifying us at [info@SearchRegistry.org](mailto:info@SearchRegistry.org) When you request us to delete your personal information, it will be deleted, but we will retain logs, demographic and statistical information about you and keep an archival copy of your information in an anonymous form. If your personal information was previously accessed by others or transferred to others using our Site, we are unable to delete the information from their systems. We have no control over the information that Ad Networks or other third parties may have about you. We encourage you to visit their websites and review and read the privacy policies and opt-out practices that govern their usage. If you change your mind about receiving communications from us, you may notify us of your preferences by [info@SearchRegistry.org](mailto:info@SearchRegistry.org) . You may also turn off cookies through your web browser. However, this may affect your use of our site as well as other's sites.

**Security**

**We endeavor to safeguard and protect your information. When you submit information at the website, such information is protected both online and offline. The servers in which we store Personal Information are kept in a secure physical environment. We have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of personal information under our control. Currently, We use Secure Socket Layer Software ("SSL") to protect data and to secure any transactions. SSL encrypts information, including credit card numbers, names and addresses as they are transmitted over the Internet. Please be advised that, although We take commercially reasonable technological precautions to protect your data, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, We cannot and do not warrant that your information will be absolutely secure. Any transmission of data at or through this site is at your own risk. However, access to your information is strictly limited, and not accessible to the public.**

**Changes to Privacy Statement**

We reserve the right to make material changes to the substance of this Privacy Statement. We will post those changes through a prominent notice on the web site so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and to whom we will disclose it

**How to Contact Us**

You may contact us for questions or concerns about our privacy practices by writing to us at:  
SearchRegistry.org  
1787 Pennsylvania Ave NW, Suite 1025  
Washington DC, 20006  
Or by Email:
